<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
        <link>http://example.org/categories/themes/</link>
        <description>Latest blog posts from My New Hugo Site</description>

        
        <language>en-us</language>
        

        

        

        

        
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        

        
        <atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/themes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        

        
            
        <item>
          <title>Brogrammers in Arms! Computer Comrades! Give us money!</title>
          <link>http://example.org/blog/id-modi/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 23:30:14 +0200</pubDate>
          
          <guid>http://example.org/blog/id-modi/</guid>
          <description>We will change the world. Step aside, Luddites! Infinite economic and technological growth is on the horizon. Many of you will be laid off, but that is a sacrifice I am willing to make. Worst case scenario, just buy some of our stock and share in the limitless capital gains of la gloire.</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>Time is, like, totally a Social Construct</title>
          <link>http://example.org/blog/tempora-maxime/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 23:21:09 +0200</pubDate>
          
          <guid>http://example.org/blog/tempora-maxime/</guid>
          <description>Time will become a mere social construct. Users will be able to absorb TikTok videos 1000x faster than what is humanly possible through the Old School, pre-2024 brain. Velocity of money will no longer be restricted to the swipe of credit cards or the counterrevolutionary compilation of code, as the general information network automates all transactions through post-blockchain technology. All enemies of the state will be identified and neutralized accordingly, whether they are foreign or domestic, real or imaginary.</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>De-materialization of the Body is Praxis</title>
          <link>http://example.org/blog/lorem/</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 16:09:23 +0200</pubDate>
          
          <guid>http://example.org/blog/lorem/</guid>
          <description>Transhumanism has finally become an indisputable reality. No more taking notes– we will have become one with information. Supercomputers will augment our reality as we’ll able to play video games, work, and spend quality time with our children simultaneously. Human solidarity is planned in the 1.1 update.</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>Guide to Silicon Valley Revolution</title>
          <link>http://example.org/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>http://example.org/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
          <description>Step 1: Just do it haha.
Step 2: Just do it but actually try haha. Step 3: Just do it, but bring on a corporate sponsor like Nike.</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>Rich Content</title>
          <link>http://example.org/blog/rich-content/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>http://example.org/blog/rich-content/</guid>
          <description>Everyone will literally become an Adam Sandler character on New Years because we think that’s funny.
This is a sacrifice everyone must be willing to make for the long-term survival of the species.</description>
        </item>
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
